ebbinteractive.com 2014-03-29

# Privacy Policy | EBB Web Design

##  Privacy Policy 

Last Updated January 12, 2013

Thank you for visiting Empowered Brand Builders, Inc. / DBA: E.B.B. Interactive / DBA: EBB Web Design – MyBrandBuilderPro (“EBB/MBBP”): website design, web development, PPC services, video production, SEO services, software development, online micro-franchises, digital marketing training, and e-commerce Internet website (“Site”) located at the URLs www.empoweredbrandbuilders.com, www.ebbwebdesign.com and www.mybrandbuilderpro.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout EBB/MBBP governing EBB/MBBP’s use of Personally Identifiable Information provided to EBB/MBBP Classroom via this Site. 

Your privacy is very important to us especially when conducting business. This Privacy Policy was created to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and security. 

## Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet’s rapidly evolving nature, EBB/MBBP may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, EBB/MBBP will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at www.mybrandbuilderpro.com so you are always aware of what Personally Identifiable Information we may collect and how we may use this information. EBB/MBBP encourages you to review this PrivacyPolicy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

Our Company collects information in many different ways from our members and visitors who access the various parts of our services through a variety of websites within our network of websites,lead capture pages and sales pages. 

We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to deliver a customized experience with certain services, products or information you have requested and to verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the Site. 

Information that we collect for non-members includes but is not always limited to name, email and phone number. For those individuals that are members of our website, we collect detailed information including but not limited to name, address, email, phone, fax, city, state, zip, social security number and credit card information for monthly billing purposes. We generally do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we either receive your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances we are required to do so by law. 

In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service providers (such as banks, merchant accounts and credit card companies) who may provide such services may collect this information from visitors and members to our Sites. 

If you are a member of our Site and post to any of the Site’s community forums, other registered users of this Site may view your username and social media links along with your email, but they will not be able to see your detailed information such as address and phone number. We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to send you advertisements and other promotional information regarding our products and services or the products and services of our third party marketing partners and other communications related to the Site. 

We will not sell your Personally Identifiable Information to any other company or organization except that we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to a successor entity upon amerger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which EBB/MBBP participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of EBB/MBBP’s assets to which this Site relates. 

## Cookies 

We use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience and for Site security. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site.

## Login Information

EBB/MBBP uses login information including but not limited to browser type and IP address to the Site to track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, External Web Sites linked to. We may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

## Advertisements

Advertisements that appear on this Site are delivered to users by EBB/MBBP and are typically for complimentary marketing products and services. Some of these products and services may be offered to visitors and members as an affiliate program. In order to provide visitors and members with these services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personally identifiable information. In these cases you will be notified by the partner and have the opportunity to decide if you want to use that particular product or service prior to any such data being collected. 

## Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which EBB/MBBP does not have control (“External Web Sites”). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by EBB/MBBP of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that EBB/MBBP is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that EBB/MBBP is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites. 

## Voluntary Member Surveys

From time to time we may conduct both personal and member base surveys. We encourage our members to participate in these surveys as it provides us will valuable data to enhance the members experience, products and services offered in the Site. Your personal information collected in any survey will remain private unless you have given us prior written permission to share specific information. 

## Age Requirement

The Site is not directed at minors. You must be eighteen (18) years or age or older to access this website. If you are under eighteen years of age, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Due to the age restrictions for use of this website, no information that is collected from this website falls within the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and is not monitored as doing so. 

## Response to Email Inquiries

In the case where a visitor or member sends an email inquiry to EBB/MBBP, we do not use the return email address for any purpose other than to respond to the request and will not share the return email address with any third party. 

## Disclosure 

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment). 

We will also disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. 

## Security 

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your Personally Identifiable Information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. EBB/MBBP may use encryption, secure socket layer, firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. While we make every effort to protect the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third party hackers from illegally obtaining this information. 

## Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information

EBB/MBBP provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. This process is done in the My Profiles section of the Site. You may access your account and review, correct and delete your Personally Identifiable Information at any time. 

You may also contact us by email at: admin@empoweredbrandbuilders.com if you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or how to delete your Personally Identifiable Information. 

Copyright 2013 Empowered Brand Builders, Inc. – DBA: E.B.B. Interactive & EBB Web Design | www.EBBwebdesign.com | www.ebbwebdesign.com  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
